Abhishek Yadav

Product Designer, UI/UX Designer



SUMMARY

Two plus years experience emphasizing product design, user experiences, and identity systems. Highly proficient in the latest industry trends, tools, and processes. Demonstrated ability to work with all levels of teammates and stakeholders to meet deadlines and produce strategic outcomes.

HISTORY

Product Designer Jan 2020 - Dec 2021

DiGiLABSItd.com

- Designed products & websites
- Developed Product standards and vision
- Created and evolved multiple identity systems

Product Designer Mar 2019 - Dec 2020

Foodifi.in

- Designed, and shipped multiple products
- Developed Product standards and vision
- Created and evolved multiple identity systems

CORRESPONDENCE

shakesheartcore@gmail.com (+91)-90051-75380

<u>abhishekyadav-</u>

shakes.web.app

SKILLS

Product Management
Product Strategy
Product Design
UI/UX Design
Web & Mobile App-Development

EDUCATION

High School Apr 2009 - Mar 2018

St. Theresa's High School - Sandila (Hardoi)